I have to go home.
My mother will kill me.
No.
Stay with me tonight.
Roman wants us to
be there at 9am.
Raya, we talked about this.
It's just a few months
working in a hotel.
Yes, but-
Do you want to work at the
printers, like your mother?
He said it was the two of us,
or nothing.
No.
Fuck your mother.
Sorry.
It's 1:30 in the morning.
You don't understand;
Luba wanted me-
If her mother lets her do what
she wants, go live there.
You've graduated.
You're an adult now.
Do what you want.
Big smile.
Good.
What will you say at the border?
I'm Natalya.
I'm Natalya Verbova.
I'm going to Budapest
to buy rugs to resell.
Raya.
Hello.
I'm working.
Leave. Leave.
Leave.
Cross-referencing
of each lesion
with other cases,
the courts considered
serious assault.
If the court decides
that to stab a man
in a bar is a crime,
the same should apply
to a woman at home.
I have considered the
evidence, and hereby find
in favor of Zlata Sehik.
Raya, are you okay?
It's me, Irka. Wake up.
Hello?
I'm calling from the Global
Displacement Agency
in Sarajevo.
Do you have a daughter
named Raya?
Yes, yes.
She is here.
If everything checks out,
we will send her home
in a few days.
I will come there now.
I'm sorry, but we can't
afford that.
I will pay. Just tell
me where to go.
Roman will be back soon.
He seems to be doing well.
Milk?
I need to borrow money.
They found Raya
in Sarajevo.
I need to go get her.
I don't need much.
Did he beat you?
You know I hate to ask,
but she is my daughter,
and his niece. Please.
I will get the money.
But you have to go.
Roman will be back soon.
He won't give me the money
if he knows it's for you.
Where's the other?
She's not here. Let's go!
We will do everything
to bring back Raya.
I'm so sorry.
What will they do to her?
I want to show you what happens
when you talk to the devil.
Now. Bring it.
Watch. Make sure they see.
Open your eyes.
Look at it.
You see your friend now!
You start work in 2 hours.
Come sleep on the free
part of the mattress.
They bring food in the morning.
You have to eat everything,
or pay a fine.
Come, sit down.
You don't look very well.
What's your name?
Raya Kochan.
I've almost paid my dues.
Then I can go home.
- It's all lies.
- No.
He returned a girl
after three months.
I was here.
What is your name?
I'm Luba. Luba Pallch.
I'm afraid we cannot keep
you here any longer.
We'll let you know if
something comes up.
We will do everything
to bring back Raya.
What is this?
- We have to leave.
- No.
You're creating problems.
Go.
I wanted to tell you.
She's how you paid for it.
Roman. He does...
How could you...
sell your own blood?
He's crazy.
- Where is she?
- I don't know.
Where is she?
She is no longer your sister.
Stay away from here.
Where is Raya, that little bitch?
She's in the back.
I said nothing!
No!
Please!